Hi, I'm Judy Carrier with Jewels by Park Lane and I'm going to tell you how to clean your sterling silver jewelry.
First of all you put a pot of water on to boil, just like you would if you're having a baby in the old movies.
Get a glass pot or an aluminum pan, either one will work.
If you have a glass pot or something just fill it, line it with aluminum foil, just plain old aluminum foil that you use on the turkey.
And then take some baking soda and sprinkle it liberally over the foil.
Put your jewelry in there.
Set it in and then you pour the hot water over it.
Now it's going to fizz up, smell kind of like rotten eggs, it's not the nicest smelling.
You let it sit there a while until it's completely dissolved and you might want to shake the pan a little or just stir it to make sure that the baking powder is completely dissolved.
And while that is cleaning, you might want to air out the windows or something, but open a window to get that smell out.
But pour the water off when it's quit fizzing and take it out, rinse it and pat it dry with a lint free cloth and your jewelry should look as good as new.
I'm Judy Carrier with Jewels by Park Lane and that's how you clean sterling silver jewelry.